Contact

latifii68@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hamedlatifi (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Front-End Development JavaScript React.js

Languages

English (Limited Working)
Persian (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

JavaScript Ultimate Guide 2022 Responsive Web Design Vue Vuex: Building Production Project (Medium Clone)

Hamed Latifi

Frontend Developer (React.js | Next.js)

Summary

I am a front-end web developer with 4 years of working experience in fields like sales, accounting and management. I combine my management expertise with technical skills and fully commit to consistency, meeting deadlines, and utilizing all available resources to achieve results.

I enjoy creating beautiful, accessible, and responsive websites using React.js, Vue.js, Vanilla JavaScript ES6+, Tailwind, Sass, CSS, and HTML.

Effective use of time, problem-solving, and communication skills help me show a positive attitude in complex situations, and my desire to learn quickly adapts me to changing situations.

Experience

ekama.ir Frontend Developer November 2021 - Present (1 year 11 months)

Self Employed
Accountant
April 2020 - November 2021 (1 year 8 months)

Amin SSD Accountant September 2018 - March 2020 (1 year 7 months) Tehran, Iran

Education

Zand University

Associate's degree, Business Management · (September 2014 - September 2016)